diginomica.com 2019-05-26

# Terms and privacy | diginomica

Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy (detailed below) govern diginomica Ltd's relationship with you in relation to this website.

## **The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:**

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * All trademarks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.
  * Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of England and Wales.

## Definition

The term diginomica.com Ltd or "us" or "we" refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is 36 Ross Road, Wallington, Surrey, SM6 8QR. Our company registration number is 8444377 registered in England and Wales. The term "you" refers to the user or viewer of our website.

References to 'website' means diginomica.com, government.diginomica.com and any other URLs owned by diginomica Ltd that we may, from time to time, launch or run.

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

## Privacy

### What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;

(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website;

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;

(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;

(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.

### Cookies

We use cookies in order to make the website work more efficiently.  Most browsers allow control of cookies through the browser settings.  However, please be aware that this may impact negatively on your use of this and other sites.

A cookie is a small text file written to your hard drive that contains information about your account on this Website. Cookies do not contain any personal information about users. During the course of your visit to this Website, the pages you see, along with a cookie, are downloaded to your device. Cookies enable us to collect useful information such as the device a user is using and whether they have visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.

### **How does diginomica use cookies**

Information gathered from cookies helps us to analyse the behaviour of our visitors and their online behaviour and patterns. This allows us to provide you with a better community and user experience by tailoring our site to your needs. We are constantly looking for ways to improve our online community and information from cookies is critical for this.

Cookies do not give us any personal information about you or your business. They simply allow us to see which areas of the site are working well i.e. visited most and which content is most of interest.

Cookies also allow you to have a more seamless experience of using the site i.e. you remain logged in for entire sessions or multiple user sessions, removing the need to remember usernames and passwords on a regular basis. Our session cookies are therefore essential to the functionality and usability of our site.

### **Third party cookies on diginomica pages**

During any visit to this Website you may notice some cookies that are not related to diginomica. These may include 3rd party advertising cookies.

You may be served a 3rd party cookie directly from one of our partners. However, 3rd party cookies only gather anonymous information. The 3rd party cookies that our partners serve simply allows ads to be shown that may be relevant to you based on previous pages and content you have viewed.

3rd party cookies will come from (among others) Doubleclick, Atlas, Yieldmanager, Google DFP, Audience Science (revsci.net).

Any widgets we use like Google+, Twitter, FB, Linkedin may also set their own cookies and set their own Google analytics cookies.

You should check the third party websites for more information about these.

### Diginomica and Google

Diginomica prides itself on the fact it carries no advertising inventory, including Google Ads. However, we do use Google Analytics for the purpose of better understanding how people use our website and where their interests lay. We also use Google Analytics in conjunction with our email newsletter system - again to track how our email newsletters are used. The statistics we gather are only used for internal reporting purposes and provide data in aggregate about visitor behaviors. No personal information is collected or provided to us except for aggregated demographic data which is collected through Google's identification algorithms.

However, as a media organization, we are aware that Google has not been exemplary in the manner in which it has approached GDPR. It has for example drawn important criticism from major media groups. A key story on this can be found [here](http://whatsnewinpublishing.com/2018/05/02/four-publishing-trade-groups-criticise-googles-ad-policy-change-letter-ceo/?utm_campaign=Revue%20newsletter&utm_medium=Newsletter&utm_source=What%27s%20New%20in%20Publishing).

While we don't anticipate any impact from the concerns raised by others, we continue to monitor the situation. Should you prefer that Google Analytics does not track your behavior or only tracks certain kinds of activity we recommend reading [this page](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2790761?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en) where you can find links to make changes in your browser. You should consider making changes consistent across all devices through which you access our website.

However, please see below about the use of cookies (of which Google makes extensive use) and the potential impact on performance.

**Update 8th May 2018**. Google asks us to confirm the time period over which we want retention of Google collected data. We have asked that from 25th May 2018, Google never automatically deletes data. The reason is so that we can get a better understanding of growth and aggregated profiles since our inception in a one time snapshot. Once that is complete, we will then use that information to determine the maximum amount of time over which it makes sense for Google to hold data for our analytical purposes. Once that is done then we will revise this page again. The change in Google's data retention permission requirement goes into effect on 25th May, 2018. You can see the data retention advisory [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196).

### **How to reject cookies?**

If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by us, you can do this through your browser settings. The Help function within your browser should tell you how. For information on how to do this on the browser of your mobile phone you should refer to your handset manual.

For accessing our local cookie settings please click here.

**Please be aware that restricting cookies will have an impact on the functionality of this website and the quality of your user experience.**

### Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a) administer the website;

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;

(d) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(e) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(f) send to you our weekly or daily newsletter where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology. You can inform us at any time if you no longer require our email newsletters and unsubscribe using tools we provide via our email newsletter service provider;

(g) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

(h) deal with inquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

### Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

### International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States and Japan) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

### Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password and firewall protected) servers.

Data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You should check to ensure that you are satisfied that your data is transmitted in as secure a manner as possible.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password nor will we have access to your password unless we are administering your account when it is directly tied to our online community.

### Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are satisfied with any changes.

### Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £25.00).

### Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

### Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [privacy@diginomica.com](mailto:den@diginomica.com) or by post to our registered office address.

### Data controller

The data controller responsible for our website is diginomica Ltd
